孩子们 2008年秋\n你们的Robin阿姨失业了还有点小落魄
Kids, in the fall of 2008,your Aunt Robin\nwas unemployed and a little bit adrift,
所以她无比重视与Lily的友情
so she valued her friendship\nwith Lily more than ever.
嘿 我听说Marshall这周五又要加班了\n你知道这意味着--女士之夜
Hey,so I hear Marshall has to work late on\nFriday. You know what that means-- ladies' night.
哦 实际上 那天我们学校一个\n叫Jillian的老师要举办生日派对
Oh,actually one of the teachers at my\nschool,Jillian, is having a birthday party.
- 好吧\n- 怎么了?
- OK.\n- What?
只是我以前从未听说过有Jillian这个人
It's just I've never even heard\nof this Jillian person before
她突然间冒出来 成为你的好友\n让你谈得滔滔不绝的
and suddenly she's,like,your best\nfriend.You can't shut up about her.
别吃醋嘛\n咱俩从来都一起玩的
Don't be jealous.You and\nI hang out all the time.
没错 但是Marshall总横在中间\n我们都没时间聊天 私下聊天
Yeah, but Marshall's always there.We don't get\na lot of quality time to talk,just the two of us.
才不是这样子呢
That's not true.
那么精彩片段开始咯
So that's when the\nstory gets really good.
那么 我们去到 嗯...
So,we go to the,uh...
那个地方 然后..
place. And then that...
那时那地那人问我关于那件事\n我跟你提过的
guy asks about that thing with the stuff\nthat I told you about at that place that time.
长话短说--惊天动地的事情发生了
Long story short--\nevents transpired.
哦 天啊
Oh,my God.
你和市长厅的那家伙做了 \n就在联合国大厦
You and the guy from the mayor's\noffice did it in the UN building
在扎伊尔大使的办公桌底下? \n妙极
under the desk of the\nAmbassador from Zaire? Nice.
我只是希望我们有些单独的女士谈心时间
I just wish we could\nhave some girl time.
我也爱Marshall \n但是他总是打断我说话
I love Marshall,but he's\nalways talk-blocking me.
那么和我一起去Jillian派对吧
So come out with me and Jillian then.
好吧 但我不想玩的太晚 \n因为...
Okay,but I don't want to\nstay out too late because...
记得上月我去那儿以后发生的事吗?
Remember that,um,thing last\nmonth after I went to the place?
嗯 你知道是谁跟我说没事\n但实际上却让我难受的很
Well,you know who said it's\nfine,but she gave me some stuff.
你那妇科病还没好?
You still got that yeast infection,huh?
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第8集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode08
Marshall 我想要你好好享受这一刻
Marshall,I want you\nto enjoy this moment.
什么一刻?
What moment?
你我之间争夺Ted的最佳好友名号的最后一刻
The last moment of you and I being even slightly\nin competion for the title of Ted's best friend.
- Marshall是我的最佳好友\n- 没错 这是个定势
- Marshall'sy best friend.\n- Exactly. It's a tie.
但是这一切都将会改变
But all of that is about to change.
Ted 你是个建筑师 \n我说得没错吧?
Ted,am I correct that\nyou are an architect?
是我的最佳好友就肯定知道的\n你接着说
My best friend would\nreally know that,but go on.
你最近在做什么设计?
And what are you currently designing?
实际上 \n我们正在翻修约克的新公共图书馆
Actually,we're renovating\nthe new York Public Library.
哇 Ted 大工程啊!
Wow,Ted,that's huge!
不 不是纽约公共图书馆
No,not the New York Public Library.
是北达科他州约克镇的新公共图书馆
It's the new public library\nin York,North Dakota.
他们的书归为两类:\n与钓鱼有关的和无关的
Their books are in two sections:\nfishin' and non-fishin'.
那么我想你一定会\n为我今天上班所发生的事而高兴的
Then I think you are going to really\nlike what happened at work today.
那么 当贿赂削弱了政权势力\n使多数的王室覆灭
And so,while those bribes did destabilize the regime\nand caused the death of most of the royal family,
它确实也使得仰光的银行规则松动
it did lead to looser banking\nregulations in Rangoon.
我们的机会来了
So yay us.
好的 会议最后一项
Okay,last order of business.
已经决定了 我们要开展新项目
It's been decided we're going\nto move forward with plans
在市中心建造戈里亚国际银行的新大厦
for Goliath National Bank's\nnew downtown headquarters.
由谁来设计?
Who's gonna design it?
这也是我的第一个问题
Was my first question.
由谁来设计?
Who's gonna design it?
我们已经和一家公司在谈了
We've already approached\none firm about it.
是个瑞典的建筑设计团队 叫Sven
This Swedish architecture\ncollective called Sven.
Sven? Sven?\nSven? Sven?
Sven就是这个瑞典的建筑设计团队\n以其大胆 创新的设计而饱受好评
Sven was this Swedish architecture collective\nrevered for their bold,innovative designs.
我恨那帮家伙
I hated those guys.
I hate those guys.
瑞典的建筑设计团队
Swedish architecture collective.
- 不靠谱\n- 自命不凡
- Lame.\n- Pretentious.
"我们不是一家公司\n我们是一个团队"
"We're not a company.\nWe're a collective."
我知道
I know.
"我们是瑞典人"
"We are Swedish.
"我们的长棍面包和埃菲尔铁塔都酷毙了"
"We are so cool with our\nbaguettes and our Eiffel Tower."
伙计 那是瑞典不是法国\n你知道的吧 对吧?
Dude,Sweden's not France.\nYou know that,right?
哦 是法国没错
Oh,it's France.
不管怎样 我跟Bilson说...
So anyway,I say to Bilson...
Bilson 怀着十万分的敬意...
Bilson,with all due respect...
不是 我站起来 我跟Bilson说...
No,I stand up,and I say to Bilson...
Bilson 怀着十万分的敬意...
Bilson,with all due respect...
来点音乐 \n想象着正在播放爱国音乐
Music. Imagine patriotic music playing.
Bilson 怀着十万分的敬意\n这事很荒唐 如果这份工作...,
Bilson,with all due respect,it\nwould be terrible if a job
它本该交给一家勤奋有为的美国建筑公司
that could go to a\nhard-workingAmerican architecture firm
却最终给了一帮法国佬来做
went to a bunch of French guys.
我们的爱国精神哪儿去了?
Where is our patriotism?
我们的民族意识呢?
Our sense of country?
我们的爱 也就是...
Our love of all that is...
听着 Stinson \n这世上没人比我更仇视别国了
Look,Stinson,no one hates every other\ncountry in the world as much as I do,
但你最好有话直说
but you better have a point.
好的
I do.
我认识个很棒的美国建筑设计师\n他非常适合这个工作
I know a fantastic American architect\nwho would be perfect for the job.
Ted Mosby\nTed Mosby.
那么 你所需要做的 就是走进去\n把你的设计丢给他们看
So,all you gotta do is\ncome in,pitch your design,
我负责说服董事会通过你的设计\n那么这份活就归你们了
I get the board to approve\nit,and the job is yours.
你知道吗 如果我能给公司揽到这个活\n我都变成公司功臣啦?
Do you realize what a hero I would be\nif I brought this project to my firm?
还有更棒的呢
And that's not even the best part.
我们三个将并肩齐战
All three of us are\ngonna be working together.
Ted也能加入电话会议了
Ted can be on the conference call.
他当然能加入电话会议啊
He can totally be on\nthe conference call.
什么是电话会议啊?
What's the conference call?
它是这么回事 我们其中一个\n偷偷潜进另一个人的办公室 说...
The way it works is,one of us will\nduck into the other's office and say...
Marshall 电话会议马上开始了
Marshall,the conference\ncall's about to start.
抱歉 伙计们 我得走了
I'm sorry,guys,I gotta go.
然后我们上到楼顶去...
And then we go up to the\nroof of the building...
喝啤酒
and drink beer.
太爽了
This is awesome.
在工作时间喝啤酒
Drinking at work.
我们是十足的疯子
We're basically Mad Men.
确实! 我们就是疯子!
We are! We're such Mad Men!
我要去摸一把秘书小姐的屁屁
I'm gonna go smack a\nsecretary on the ass.
电影里他们就是这么演的
That's totally what they\nwould do on that show.
什么电影?
What show?
然后 \n我们拿揉成一团的啤酒罐去扔鸽子
And then,we throw crumpled\nup beer cans at pigeons.
我可没做
I don't do that.
我很想加入
I totally want to do that.
好吧 我来安排
Well,I am gonna make that happen.
说真的 Barney 在我从Stella的旧伤中复原后\n能得到这个机会...
Seriously,Barney,after everything I went through\nwith Stella,getting me this opportunity...
真的是太重要
it really means a lot.
确实如此
It really did.
孩子们  当我成为建筑师的时候 \n一直有个梦想
You see,kids,when I became\nan architect,I had one dream--
在纽约的摩天大厦风景线上也有自己的一笔
to contribute a building to\nthe skyline of New York City.
我想要指出其中某座楼问别人\n看到那座楼了嘛?
I wanted to be able to point to one of\nthose buildings and say,see that one?
就是那边的那座?
That one right there?
那是我设计的
That's mine.
这工作将是我实现梦想的机会
This job was my\nopportunity to do just that.
你的朋友在这办生日派对?
Your friend's having her birthday here?
她过几岁生日啊 19?
What's she turning,19?
不是的 相信我 \n这不是她的风格
No. Believe me,this isn't her scene.
她可能只是不知道这地方会是这样的
She probably just didn't know\nwhat kind of place this was.
Lily! 过来 你个性感的小贱人! \n我们买了酒哦!
Lily! Over here,you sexy\nbitch! We've got bottle service!
哦 天啊 在学校的时候 \n她可是很文静很正常的啊
Oh,my God. At school,she's\nso quiet and normal.
我也不晓得她怎么...
I had no idea she's...
她是个"尖叫女"
she's a Woo Girl.
什么是"尖叫女"? 容我解释一下
What's a Woo Girl? Let me explain.
尖叫女是年轻的女人 \n她们尖笑起来像布谷鸟或北美夜鹰一样
A Woo Girl is a type of young woman,who,like\nthe cuckoo bird or the whip-poor-will,
从她那典型的叫声中可知此名由来
gets her name from the\nsignature sound she makes.
那么 有几种事情可以触发尖叫女
Now,a woo can be elicited\nin many different ways.
听到点唱机的某首歌...
From a certain song\ncoming on the jukebox...
哦 天啊 这首歌就是为我写的啊
Oh,my God,this song is totally about me.
打了折的酒
to half-priced shots.
骑电子公牛...
From a ride on a mechanical bull...
实际上 也许什么事情都能让她们尖叫
to,well,pretty much anything.
哦 天啊 我担心还没喂猫呢\n后来发现我喂了
Oh,my God,I was worried that I didn't feed\nthe cat,but then I rembered that I did.
我发誓 在学校的时候\nJillian看起来可没有半点尖叫的样子
I swear,at school\nJillian seems so un-woo-y.
没错 她看着不像会尖叫样子
Yeah,she doesn't look wooish.
也许她只是在狂欢节啊 春假之类的时候\n才上演这种保留曲目
Maybe she only observes the high\nholidays,like Mardi Gras and Spring Break.
也许她只是文艺尖叫女
Maybe she's just a cultural Woo.
那么 嗯 别抱太大期望啊
Now,uh,go easy on me.
还只是个草稿
It's a work in progress.
Ted 这太棒了
Ted,this is amazing.
这些细节 这些形状\n这些调皮的线条
The detail. The shading.\nThe playfulness of the lines.
这就像莱亚公主没戴帽子的样子\n（星球大战公主)
This is exactly what Princess\nLeia would look like topless.
当我说了谢谢吧
My way of saying thanks.
那么 嗯 \n你想要看看我的设计么?
So,uh,you want to see my\ndesigns for the building?
不用了
Nah,I'm good.
听着 刚刚Lily发短信给我
So get this. Lily just texted me.
她在Giddyups酒吧里\n和一群尖叫女在一起
She's at that bar Giddyups\nwith a bunch of Woo Girls.
哦 天啊 姐儿们 \n刚在吧台那我的咪咪露点了
Oh,my God,you guys,my boob just\nfell out of my top at the bar.
骗你们的! 我自己扯露出来的 \n为了免费啤酒!
Trick! I pulled it out for a free drink!
那么 Jillian 我听说当你\n不与调酒师调情的时候 你教中班啊
So,Jillian,I hear when you're not flashing\nbartenders,you teach the second grade.
感觉怎么样?
What's that like?
感到不胜荣耀
So rewarding.
我不知道你是否了解RIE教学法
I don't know if you're\nfamiliar with the RIE technique,
但是它是基于Rudolf Steiner的\n循序渐进教学理论产生的
but it derives from the progressive\neducational philosophy of Rudolf Steiner,
他建立了Waldorf学校 它...
who founded the Waldorf School,which...
哦 天啊 我爱死这首歌了!
Oh,my God. I love this song!
来吧 你们这些懒婊子 咱去跳舞吧!
Come on,you lazy skanks,let's dance!
还有你 你个死贱人
You,too,you dumb whores.
不了 多谢...
No,thank you...
我们是纯情少女呢
ya ignorant hussy.
为什么 Lily Aldrin 你个狡猾的女人
Why,Lily Aldrin,you sly minx.
我早就说过我们的小团体\n需要这么一个尖叫女
I've been saying for years\nthat our gang need a Woo Girl,
你却把一个尖叫团都给我藏起来了啊
and here you've been hiding\na whole batch of them from me.
我们不需要尖叫女\n没人需要尖叫女
We do not need a Woo Girl.\nNo one needs a Woo Girl.
你要注意咯 Lily
Be careful,Lily.
世界绝对需要尖叫女
The world absolutely needs Woo Girls.
如果没有尖叫女\n就不会有狂野女
If there were no Woo\nGirls,there'd be noGirls Gone Wild,
没有告别单身节\n没有拉斯维加斯池畔酒吧的狂欢...
no bachelorette parties,no\nLas Vegas poolside bars...
你所拥有的一切美好事物 Lily\n都会消失
all the things that you hold\ndearest,Lily,would be gone.
那都是些破事儿...
Those are none of the things...
工艺礼品产业将会倒闭
The souvenir shot glass\nindustry would collapse.
还有涂体闪粉化妆行业\n和悍马车出租业都会倒闭
So would the body glitter industry\nand the stretch Hummer rental industry.
小牛仔帽就真的的只有小牛仔才会戴
Tiny cowboy hats would be\nworn only by tiny cowboys.
当点唱机播放棕眼女孩组合的歌\n你们能听到的...
And when "Brown Eyed Girl" would come\nup on the jukebox,all you would hear...
只是一片寂静
would be silence.
还有棕眼女孩的演唱而已
And "Brown Eyed Girl."
但是谁会尖叫呢 Lily?
But who would woo,Lily?
但是谁会尖叫呢? 你会吗?
Who would woo? Would you?
你会吗...
Would you...
谁想给我咪咪取个名啊?
Who wants to name my boobs?
那么抱歉了 \n我和Hannity以及Colmes有约了
Now if you'll excuse me,I have\na date with Hannity and Colmes.
接下来几周 我埋头工作
Over the next couple of\nweeks,I dove into work.
从事真正在乎的工作 \n我感到很开心
It felt great to be working on\nsomething that I really cared about.
最后 展示我设计的那个早上到来了
Finally,the morning of\nthe presentation arrived.
我们深信这个永恒的设计能够反应出
And we believe this timeless\ndesign will radiate the strength
戈里亚国际银行的力量和不朽
and stability that is\nGoliath National Bank.
谢谢 先生们
Thank you,gentlemen.
我满怀着机遇的欣喜离开了公司
I left there feeling pretty\ngood about my chances.
晚上 我们碰见了Barney
Later that night,we ran into Barney.
嘿 Barney!
Hey,Barney!
告诉我好消息
Give me the good news.
你没中标
You didn't get it.
什么?
What?
董事会决定与Sven合作
The board decided to go with Sven.
真难以置信 我没中标
I can't believe I didn't get it.
我真的以为自己已经十拿九稳了
I really thought I nailed the pitch.
他们怎么会选择Sven的?
Why would they go with Sven?
我尽了全力来改变他们的主意
I did everything I could\nto change their minds.
但他们就是不让步
But they wouldn't budge.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
哦 这太糟糕了
Wow,this really sucks.
经过这几个月时间
After the way these last\ncouple of months have gone...
我觉得我比我预计的更需要这个工作
I guess I need this more\nthan I thought I did.
你是不是想去现在的戈里亚国际银行大厦 \n然后比方说
You want to go down to the current\nGNB building and just,like...
我也不知道 在上面撒泡尿?
I don't know,just pee\non it a little bit?
嗯 是 我想我是需要
Yeah. Yeah,I think I need that.
把酒喝完
Finish your beer.
怎么了?
What happened?
哦 Ted没得到那个工作
Oh,Ted didn't get that job.
但那不是今天最令人失望的事
But that's not the biggest\ndisappointment of the day.
什么?
What?
我们看见你尖叫了
We saw you woo.
看谁尖叫了?
Saw who woo?
你尖叫了啊
Sawyouwoo.
我不可能啊
I didn't woo.
- 就是你没错\n- 这不是真的
- You did,too.\n- That's not true.
你的鼻子都长了
Your nose just grew.
你好像现在成了Jillian的密友了?
You're,like,best\nfriends with Jillian now?
不是 只不过...
No. It's just...
你结婚了 Lily 可我仍然是单身
You're married,Lily,but\nI'm still single.
无论什么时候我跟你在一起\n我总觉得我是你跟Marshall之间的电灯泡
Whenever I hang out with you,I'm usually\nthe third wheel to you and Marshall.
有时跟其他单身女人一起出去 做一些\n你不喜欢做的事情 是很有意思的
Sometimes,it's fun to go out with other single\nwomen and do stuff that you don't want to.
比如什么?
Like what?
比如尖叫 Lily 就比如尖叫
Like woo,Lily. Like woo.
- 我可以尖叫的\n- 这不是真的
- I can woo.\n- That's not true.
- 我也可以的\n- 那就不是你了
- I can,too.\n- It's just not you.
- Bilson
- 怎么了?
- Bilson.\n- Yeah?
听着 我只是 我只是想说\n我知道你们支持Sven
Look,I just...I just want to\nsay,I know you guys went with Sven,
但是Ted Mosby非常有天赋
but Ted Mosby is tremendously talented,
我觉得他可以把这个工作做得非常不错
and I think he would\nhave done a hell of a job.
我同意 这就是为什么我投他的票了
I agree. That's why I voted for him.
这么说你们同意了
So,then,it's agreed.
从今以后所有ATM机收费现在\n叫做为自由而付费
From now on,all ATM fees are\nnow called Freedom Charges.
电话会议 现在
Conference call. Now.
你有什么想跟我说的?
You got something you want to tell me?
哦 该死的
Oh,damn it.
我告诉过Heather把所有东西\n都按原样放回你桌子上
I told Heather to put everything\nback on your desk the way it was.
Bilson告诉我他想把那个工作给Ted\n那么发生了什么?
Bilson told me he wanted to give\nthe job to Ted. So what happened?
哦 好吧
Okay,fine.
将反映出戈里亚国际银行的力量和不朽
will radiate the strength and\nstability that is Goliath National Bank.
谢谢 先生们
Thank you,gentlemen.
怎么样?
So?
很好啊 我喜欢它
That was great. I love it.
对! 看起来我们找对了人
Yes! Looks like we got our guy.
我看根本用不着再见那个 呃...
I don't think we even\nneed to meet with,uh...
我是Sven Jorgensen
I am Sven Jorgensen.
我旁边的是Sven Pilsen和Sven Johanssen\n我们是...
With me are Sven Pilsen and\nSven Johanssen,and we are...
Sven!\nSven!
你是戈里亚国际银行
You are Goliath National Bank.
你是前沿 你是新的 是崭新的
You are cutting edge. You\nare new. You are fresh.
女人想跟你在一起 男人想伤害你
Women want to be with\nyou,men wish to harm you,
但是想挑战你的傻子会被击败!
but the fool who dares\nchallenge you shall be crushed!
你的总部要告诉世界这些事实
Your headquarters will tell\nthe world of these facts.
哦 还有一件事...现在别看!
Oh,and one more thing... Don't look now!
哪位是Barney Stinson 遴选委员会主席?
Which of you is Barney Stinson,head\nof the search committee?
哦 天啊 说我呢!
Oh,my God. That's me!
你 Barney Stinson是个有力量和男子气概的人
You,Barney Stinson,are a\nman of power and virility.
你的办公室应该在这里 在暴龙Rex的头部
Your office shall be here,in\nthe head of a Tyrannosaurus rex.
我刚刚才知道这就是我一直以来的梦想
I never knew it till now,but\nI've always dreamed of that.
在你洪都拉斯红木的大桌子上面\n会有这个按钮
On your large desk of Honduran\nrosewood shall be this button.
这个按钮是干什么的?
What does the button do?
按一下! 为了荣誉按一下!
Press it! Press it for glory!
好极了!
Yes!
这是宇宙间最帅的建筑
This is the most awesome\nbuilding in the universe.
这个建筑再不可能更帅了
There is no way this building\ncould be more awesome.
字母N里面还设计了个脱衣舞俱乐部
There is a strip club in the letter "N."
你到底有什么毛病啊?
What the hell is the matter with you?
这是Ted的重大突破!
This is Ted's big break!
然后你把他出卖了\n只因为你想工作在暴龙Rex的脑袋里
And then you sold him out because you wanted\nto work in the brain of a Tyrannosaurus rex,
顺便提一句 如果你稍微了解恐龙的话\n它们的头是非常非常小的
which,incidentally,if you knew anything\nabout dinosaurs,is really,really small.
Marshall 这跟我的办公室没有关系
Marshall,this isn't about my office.
Ted的方案是不错
Ted's building was good.
Sven的更好
Sven's was better.
我不能让我是Ted最好的朋友\n这一个原因影响我的工作
And I am not going to let the fact that I\nam Ted's best friend be a factor in business.
你挑了Sven的方案不是因为那个更好
You didn't pick Sven's\nbuilding because it was better.
你挑了那个是因为你想工作\n在一个很酷的恐龙办公室里
You picked it because you wanted\nto work in a cool dinosaur office.
这是撒谎!
That's a lie!
我选它是因为 因为...
I picked it because it-it...
它会喷火 Marshall
It breathes fire,Marshall.
"开除了Marshall"
"Fire Marshall."
我都没注意到
I didn't even notice.
你怎么能这样对Ted呢\n尤其在Stella事件发生之后?
How could you do this to Ted after\neverything he's been through with Stella?
你真是太自私了
You're just being selfish.
Marshall 我绝对不会出于个人目的\n做商业决策
Marshall,I wouldnever ma a business\ndecision for selfish reasons.
我很专业
I am a professional.
现在 来吧
Now,come on.
我们白天喝醉了吧 然后用空酒罐砸鸽子
Let's get a nice daytime drunk\ngoing,and throw empties at pigeons.
不 不 因为两个原因
No. No. For two reasons.
一是因为鸽子可比你想象中聪明的多 \n它们记仇的
One,pigeons are smarter than\nyou think. They hold grudges.
二是因为这是咱们最后一次电话会议\nStinson先生
And,two,this is our last\nconference call,Mr. Stinson.
这就是算计朋友的后果
There are repercussions\nto screwing over a friend.
- 比如什么?\n- 比如这样
- Like what?\n- Like this.
哦 天啊 姐们儿
Oh,my God,you guys.
昨天晚上我们为我的慈善晚会募捐了1万块\n帮助那些读写困难症的孩子
Last night,we raised $10,000 for my\ncharity to help combat childhood illiteracy.
这是个很重大的问题
It's a really serious issue.
有人刚刚赢得了第一个走进舞池的机会
Someone just earned herself an ass-first\nride down the dance floor spank canyon!
Lily 你来干什么?
Lily,what are you doing here?
哦 只不过做些你们单身女孩\n才做的有趣的事情
Oh,just doing the fun\nthings you single girls do.
那个救火队塑料帽子是干什么的?
What's with the plastic fireman's hat?
哦 我没有牛仔帽 \n今天是学校消防安全日 所以...
Oh,I didn't have a cowboy hat,and today\nwas fire safety day at school,so...
哦 天啊 贱人 这是我们的颂歌
Oh,my God,bitch. This is our anthem.
真的吗? 谁唱的?
Really? Who sings this?
LL Cool J还唱吗?\n(美国东海岸著名Hip-Hop老歌手)
Is LL Cool J still doing things?
这很好 Svens
This is great,Svens.
你们这些家伙比Marshall酷多了
You guys are so much\ncooler than Marshall.
他连个紧身衣都没有
He doesn't even own a unitard.
谁想要喝点酒?
Who wants a brew?
我不明白
I don't understand.
电话会议在哪里?
Where is the conference call?
这就是电话会议 明白吗?
Thisisthe conference call. Get it?
在美国如果我们工作到很晚 \n我们就撒谎说要开会
In America,when we work\nlate,welieabout a conference call,
然后我们来这里喝点啤酒
and we come up here and\nwe drink a few beers.
真是棒极了
It's awesome.
这是浪费时间
This is a waste of time.
俯卧撑!
Push-ups!
Misty 你真是个荡妇
Misty,you are such a slut.
我们再喝一杯
Let's do another shot.
你这个小贱人\n这一杯你买单
You're the slut,you\nskank. Shots are on you.
不 贱人 你买单差不多
No,bitch,shots are on you.
你个婊子
You're such a whore.
你们真是一群妓女 你们也许有性病
You're all a bunch of prostitutes.\nYou probably have STDs.
我们去跳舞吧
Let's go dance.
Lily 这不适合你 你不该在这里
Lily,this isn't working.\nYou shouldn't be here.
哦 我明白了
Oh,I get it.
因为我幸福的结婚了 我就是个失败者?
Because I'm happily\nmarried,I'm some kind of loser?
恰恰相反
Exactly the opposite.
Lily 你觉得那些尖叫女孩为什么\n因为一杯酒或者一个游戏
Lily,why do you think the Woo Girls have\nto woo when they win a game of beer pong,
再或者勾搭上一个帅哥\n就不得不尖叫?
or when a hot guy takes his shirt off?
那是因为生活的精彩也不过如此
It's because that is as\ngood as life gets for them.
她们是真正悲伤的人
They're really sad people.
当她们跟一个什么都有了的人出来玩时
And,when they hang out with someone\nwho's got it all figured out--
比如你\n他们会很沮丧的
someone like you--\nit bums them out.
所以在你面前她们尖叫不起来
It takes away their woo.
你这样说只不过为了不让我觉得\n自己是个已婚的老女人
You're just saying that so I don't\nfeel like an old married lady.
看看那些女孩 Lily
Look at those girls,Lily.
看看她们 \n听听她们的尖叫实际上是在说什么
Look at them and listen to what\ntheir woo's are really saying.
我洗澡的时候会哭!
********
我从来没有过第二次约会!
*************
如果我永远做不了母亲怎么办?!
*****************
我暗恋Jillian!
*********************
我的事业和爱情都虚无缥缈
*************************
哦 那些可怜的女孩 还有Ted
Oh,those poor girls... a-and Ted.
我 我只想过去给她们个拥抱
I-I just want to go\ngive them all a hug.
Lily 现在我跟她们差不多
Lily,right now I'm like them.
我失业了 单身 我有些迷茫
I'm unemployed,I'm\nsingle,I'm a little lost.
所以时不时的我也要尖叫放纵一下
So every once in a while,I need to woo,
但是如果我真的想谈心
but when I need to talk\nabout something real,
我会去找你的
you're the one I turn to.
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend.
你也是我的最好的朋友
And you're mine.
我保证我会多腾出些时间给我们俩
And I promise I'll make\nmore time for just us.
Marshall不必我们做什么都掺合进来
Marshall doesn't have to tag\nalong to everything we do.
嘿 你们试过这紫色试管酒吗?
Hey,have you guys tried these\npurple hooter test tube shots?
我喝了五六杯 \n我觉得这玩意儿都没度数的
I've had,like,five of 'em. I don't\neven think there's alcohol in here.
- 你从哪搞来的那个帽子?\n- 什么帽子?
- Where'd you get that hat?\n- What hat?
- 我们不用Sven了\n- 什么?
- We fired Sven.\n- What?
嗯 那些家伙是白痴
Yeah,those guys were idiots.
我的意思是 当然 他们想法很酷\n有些真的非常酷
I mean,sure,they had some cool\nideas-- some really cool ideas.
事实上我怀疑现在是不是太晚...
Actually,I wonder if\nit's not too late to...
不!
No!
关键问题是 你得到了这个工作
The point is: you got the job.
- 真的吗?\n- 对
- Really?\n- Yeah.
遴选委员会意识到他们犯了个错误
The search committee realized\nthey made the wrong decision.
另外 你对他们真的很重要 \n他们希望你能开心
Plus,you really mean a lot to\nthem and they want you to be happy.
好奇怪呀
That's weird.
听着 Ted 你的设计是最好的 \n你受之无愧
Look,Ted,your design was\nthe best,and you deserve it.
还有为什么你一开始没被选中\n我得跟你说点实话
There's also something that you should know about\nwhy you didn't get the job in the first place.
- 你听着 Ted...\n- 是因为Bilson
- You see,Ted...\n- It was Bilson.
对 对
Yeah,yeah.
Bilson就想要个恐龙脑袋里的办公室
Bilson just wanted to have\nan office in a dinosaur head,
不过Barney说服他那很傻
but Barney convinced him that\nit was really,really stupid.
是啊 你知道的
Well,you know.
谢谢你 Barney
Thank you,Barney.
我不敢相信 我...我刚刚得到了\n我们公司创建以来最大的客户
I can't believe this. I-I just got our\nfirm the biggest account we've ever had.
现在只有我的爱情还在飘渺了!
**********
下一轮我请
Next round's on me.
为什么你没告发我?
Why'd you let me off the hook?
你做了件正确的事
You did the right thing.
看起来你不该被告发
Seemed like you deserved a bye.
另外 那件事真的让Ted很失望\n他现在 现在终于...
Plus,it would have really bummed\nTed out,and he's-he's finally...
- 高兴起来了\n- 是啊
- happy right now.\n- Yeah.
你真是Ted最好的朋友
You really are Ted's best friend.
我也是 这是不言而喻的
And so am I. It's a tie.
谢谢你 Marshall
Thanks,Marshall.
Marshall不服输 \n大概十分钟后告诉我关于Barney的事
Marshall wound up caving and telling me the\ntruth about Barney,like,ten minutes later,
于是我们把Barney叔叔捆在机械公牛上
at which point we tied Uncle\nBarney to the mechanical bull,
把手柄转到"七荤八素"档 然后回家了
cranked it up to a setting called\n"Paint Mixer" and went home.
- 我爱你 伙计\n- 我也爱你 伙计
- I love you,man.\n- Love you,too,buddy.
嘿 你今天晚上想骑公牛吗?
Hey,you going to ride the bull tonight?
不 即使你请客我也不骑
No,not if you paid me.
我内耳有问题
I have an inner ear thing.
这是个愉快的晚上
It was a pretty great night.
三小时 破了酒吧的纪录
Three hours. That's a bar record.
没错 女士们
That's right,ladies.
Jillian 你知道今天晚上有什么\n疯狂有趣愚蠢的事可做吗?
Jillian,you know what'd be really crazy\nand funny and stupid to do tonight?
如果我们找到一个男人玩3p
If you and me find a\nguy and have a three-way.
也许... 如果我们找的到合适的人
Maybe... if we found the right guy.
嗯 不过...
Yeah,and...
如果我们找不到合适的人 \n也许咱们俩可以...
if we don't find the right\nguy,maybe you and I could just...
你知道我发现谁很可爱吗?
You know who was pretty cute?
那个叫Ted的家伙
That guy Ted.
我们去找他吧
Let's go find him.